Let's take a quick look at some of the key things that Flexbox can do.
让我们来快速看一些弹性盒子能做的事
I'm going to do that without giving too much explanation,
在这里我不会太多的解释它们
just because I want to give you an idea of what Flexbox is.
只是想让你看看弹性盒子是怎么个情况
Then step-by-step, we'll go through and teach how to do each of them.
稍后我们会一步一步依次学习它们
Here, you can see that I have set up.
这里你可以看见一个基础文件
Let's take a look at the HTML first,
先来看看 HTML 代码
a div with a class container,
这里有一个类名为 container 的 div
and then inside of that,
在它内部
I have three divs with the class box,
有 3 个带有 box 类名的 div
and each of them has a different ID,
每一个有着不同的 ID 属性
one, two, and three.
1、2、3
So one thing I could do is simply change my flex direction from column to row,
首先 我们将 flex-direction 属性 从 column 设置为 row
and you see that it has changed the alignment of the boxes inside.
可以看到 内部 box 元素的排列对齐方式就被改变了
So now if you look,
可以看到
you can see that my three boxes are in a row.
现在 3 个 box 元素排成了一行显示
But again, column and they are in a column.
如果我们改回 column 的话 它们又会重新排成一列
What about column reverse?
那么 column-reverse 属性呢 ?
So here it's box one,
这里是 box 1
box two, box three.
box 2 和 box 3
Now, that we refreshed it's box three,
现在我们刷新一下 它变成了
box two, box one.
box 3、box 2 和 box 1
Let's go back to a row for a second.
现在 让我们回到排列成行的状态
Let's try changing how we justify our content.
试试改变元素对齐的方式
You can see that each of the three boxes
你也可以看到每个 box 都有一些
also have some of their own individual CSS properties.
各自的 CSS 属性
The one that I want us to look at right this second is just called order.
这里我们重点关注 order 属性
Right now they all have an order of one.
现在他们的 order 属性都是 1
So there are ordered one, two, three.
所以它们按顺序依次排列
But watch what happens when I drop the order of one and
让我们试试 把 box 1 和 box 2 的 order 属性改为 3
two to three and leave the order property of div three at one.
然后依旧保持 box 3 的 order 属性为 1 看看会发生什么
You see that box three is now first because it comes in
可以看到 box 3 现在排列在了第一个位置
the order or of columns like this.
因为它们是按照 order 来排列的 垂直排列看起来是这样
If we don't want to align in the item center,
如果我们不想居中的话
we move them over there.
我们就删除掉这行
There's all stuff that you can do once you start to take control with Flexbox.
好了 这就是你学习弹性盒子后可以做的事情了
Let's dive deeper so that you can learn the real skills underlying
让我们更深入地了解一下 这样你就可以真正掌握
the movements we're making and set up your pixel perfect website.
这些技术 去完成你自己的像素级完美网站